{
    "cards": [
        {
            "front": "が",
            "back": "ga"
        },
        {
            "front": "ぎ",
            "back": "gi"
        },
        {
            "front": "ぐ",
            "back": "gu"
        },
        {   
            "front": "げ",
            "back": "ge"
        },
        {
            "front": "ご",
            "back": "go"
        },
        {
            "front": "ざ",
            "back": "za"
        },
        {
            "front": "じ",
            "back": "ji"
        },
        {
            "front": "ず",
            "back": "zu"
        },
        {
            "front": "ぜ",
            "back": "ze"
        },
        {
            "front": "ぞ",
            "back": "zo"
        },
        {
            "front": "だ",
            "back": "da"
        },
        {
            "front": "ぢ",
            "back": "ji"
        },
        {
            "front": "づ",
            "back": "dzu"
        },
        {
            "front": "で",
            "back": "de"
        },
        {
            "front": "ど",
            "back": "do"
        },
        {
            "front": "ば",
            "back": "ba"
        },
        {
            "front": "び",
            "back": "bi"
        },
        {
            "front": "ぶ",
            "back": "bu"
        },
        {
            "front": "べ",
            "back": "be"
        },
        {
            "front": "ぼ",
            "back": "bo"
        },
        {
            "front": "ぱ",
            "back": "pa"
        },
        {
            "front": "ぴ",
            "back": "pi"
        },
        {
            "front": "ぷ",
            "back": "pu"
        },
        {
            "front": "ぺ",
            "back": "pe"
        },
        {
            "front": "ぽ",
            "back": "po"
        },
        {
            "front": "ガ",
            "back": "ga"
        },
        {
            "front": "ギ",
            "back": "gi"
        },
        {
            "front": "グ",
            "back": "gu"
        },
        {   
            "front": "ゲ",
            "back": "ge"
        },
        {
            "front": "ゴ",
            "back": "go"
        },
        {
            "front": "ザ",
            "back": "za"
        },
        {
            "front": "ジ",
            "back": "ji"
        },
        {
            "front": "ズ",
            "back": "zu"
        },
        {
            "front": "ゼ",
            "back": "ze"
        },
        {
            "front": "ゾ",
            "back": "zo"
        },
        {
            "front": "ダ",
            "back": "da"
        },
        {
            "front": "ヂ",
            "back": "ji"
        },
        {
            "front": "ヅ",
            "back": "dzu"
        },
        {
            "front": "デ",
            "back": "de"
        },
        {
            "front": "ド",
            "back": "do"
        },
        {
            "front": "バ",
            "back": "ba"
        },
        {
            "front": "ビ",
            "back": "bi"
        },
        {
            "front": "ブ",
            "back": "bu"
        },
        {
            "front": "ベ",
            "back": "be"
        },
        {
            "front": "ボ",
            "back": "bo"
        },
        {
            "front": "パ",
            "back": "pa"
        },
        {
            "front": "ピ",
            "back": "pi"
        },
        {
            "front": "プ",
            "back": "pu"
        },
        {
            "front": "ペ",
            "back": "pe"
        },
        {
            "front": "ポ",
            "back": "po"
        }
    ]
}